http://www.pitheatre.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | Pi Theatre
Skip to main content
Main Menu
HomeAbout UsPi Theatre's MissionOur HistoryStaffBoard of DirectorsAwardsBlogAssociates2018 - 2019 Associates2017 - 2018 Associates2016 - 2017 Associates2015 - 2016 AssociatesPrime PlacementsPi's VideosWhat's OnEncounter:
A Cabin Fever FundraiserPi Programming NewsA Wake For Lost TimeLampedusaAprès le Déluge: The Buddy Cole MonologuesIn Response to AlabamaShakespeare's EMCalendarPast ShowsDonate to Pi2020-2021 Season DonationOur Donors & SponsorsGet InvolvedBecome a Member!Join the BoardVolunteersPrime Placements ApplicationAuditionsContactMembershipCart
Privacy Policy
This site complies with the following Privacy Policy. By using this site, you indicate your acceptance of our Online Privacy Policy.
This site collects no personally identifying information about individuals except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. We do record information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address when you interact with the site. We use this information to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. We also use this information to verify the number of discrete times you visit this web site each day.
In addition, we may place a "cookie" in the browser files of a user's computer. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information although it will enable us to relate a user's use of our sites to information that the user has specifically and knowingly provided to us.
A user's personally identifying information may be used for marketing and promotional purposes and we may share the information with others if the user has not advised us of his or her preference not to be included in such an exchange. Individuals always have the ability to stop their information being used for such purposes.
We may send e-mail to people with whom we have a business relationship.
To ensure the security of your data, including address information and credit card numbers, We always uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures that protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you.
While we will seek to require third parties with whom we have agreements to follow appropriate privacy policies, we do not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties. Our web site contains links, including e-commerce opportunities with affiliates, partners and associates, to other sites that are not maintained by us. If you visit these sites, please look for their privacy policy.
TwitterFacebook
Upcoming
Sorry, there are no posts at this time.
View Calendar
eNewsletter
Subscribe to our newsletter and get the latest news, updates and exclusive offers. You can unsubscribe at anytime.
